erai-raws.info 2019-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Erai-raws

**This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.**

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?  
****We do not collect information from visitors of our site.**  
**or other details to help you with your experience.**

**When do we collect information?  
****We collect information from you when you provide us with feedback on our products or services When roaming the site.**

**How do we use your information?  
****• To improve our website in order to better serve you.**  
**• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.**

**How do we protect your information?  
****We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.**  
**An external PCI compliant payment gateway handles all CC transactions.**  
**We use regular Malware Scanning.  
****Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.**

**Do we use ‘cookies’?  
****Yes.**

**We use cookies to:**  
**• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.**  
**• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.  
****You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
****If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.**

**Third-party disclosure  
****We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.  
****However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.**

**Third-party links  
****Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.**

**Google  
****Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.  
https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
****Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.**

**We have implemented the following:**  
**• Google Display Network Impression Reporting**  
**• DoubleClick Platform Integration**

**We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.**

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  
**It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking**

**You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page**

**By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you don’t agree to this policy, please don’t use this site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.**

**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.**

**Erai-Raws**  
**admin-erai@erai-raws.info**

**Last Edited on 27/12/2017**
